# Frank Sebastian Riaño Cano

#### **UX/UI DESIGNER - FRONTEND DEVELOPER**

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## BootNetwork UX Copywriter

Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

- Worked for 6 months as a UX copywriter at BootNetwork, a US-based company.
- Redesigned and rewrote content for various web pages.
- Wrote persuasive and engaging copy to improve user experience and increase conversions.
- Conducted A/B testing to evaluate the performance of different copies and designs.
- Achieved a 30% increase in traffic and sales through my work.

### Teleperformance, Sutherland, Webhelp OneLink Customer Service in English

Aug 2018 - Apr 2023

- Remote support through chat or voice to foreign customers.
- Winner of several personal and group performance bonuses.
- Improved user opinion scores of the service lines.
- Management of information and communication management tools.

### YouAndEnglish English Teacher

Oct 2020 - Aug 2021

- Taught English to students from Spain aged 13 to 68, both male and female, from level A1.
- Helped students reach B1 level and pass English language exams for their studies.
- Managed virtual teaching tools and implemented personalized methodologies according to the student.

#### **LinkedIn Profile:**

linkedin.com/in/sirfrank0/

frankseb04@gmail.com Bogotá D.C, Colombia https://sirfrank0.netlify.app/

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a UX/UI design and Frontend programming professional with experience in successful mobile application and website design projects. My experience includes using tools such as Figma, Webflow, HTML, CSS, and Javascript to create attractive and functional user interfaces. In addition, I have soft skills in teamwork, effective communication, and problemsolving. I am excited to apply my skills and knowledge to a new job challenge.



## Check here my portfolio:

sirfrank0.netlify.app/#portfolio

#### **RELEVANT SKILLS**

- CSS, HTML, JavaScript, React.
- Figma, AdobeXD, Sketch.
- WordPress, Webflow.
- Git, Github.
- UX copywriting and web content improvement
- Systems design use.
- Teamwork and collaboration skills
- Excellent communication skills in Spanish and English
- Project management and deadlineoriented.
- Attention to detail and focus on quality work.
- Spanish Native level
- English High level

#### **Teleperformance**

#### **Team metrics management**

Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

- Evaluated the work of customer service team members.
- Managed and calculated numbers related to the performance of each member of the team
- Achieved maximum score in quality during the time as an analyst on the line.
- Maintained good relationship and communication with agents.
- Achieved a 40% increase in quality scoresa from the agents.

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

# Software Development Universidad Nacional Abierta y a Distancia (UNAD) 2022 - Now

- Introduction to programming fundamentals and software development methodologies
- Proficiency in programming languages such as Java, Python, and JavaScript.
- Understanding of database management and web application development.

# Frontend Developer - User Interface (UI) Designer - User Experience (UX) Designer Platzi 2017 - 2022

- Proficiency in design tools such as Figma, Sketch, and Adobe Creative Suite
- Experience in creating responsive designs for mobile and desktop devices
- Ability to create attractive and functional user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

## Bachelor's degree in English and Spanish - Systems Engineering.

#### Antonio Nariño College 2019 - Now

- Comprehensive knowledge of the English and Spanish languages, including grammar, literature, and linguistics
- Understanding of software engineering principles and methodologies
- Proficiency in programming languages such as Java, C++, and Python, as well as web development technologies like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### MetroApp Platzi , Torresburriel Estudio -2021

- Designed the interface for a mobile application that streamlines public transportation in a fictional city.
- Employed User Journeys and User Personas to develop a seamless user experience.
- Used popular prototyping tools like Figma, Canva, and Whimsical to bring the vision to life
- Recognized as one of the top 10 projects out of hundreds according to industry experts at Platzi and Torresburriel Estudio.

### My website Personal - 2022

- Crafted a stunning online portfolio showcasing personal and professional achievements.
- Leveraged cutting-edge technologies like Flex and Grid with CSS to optimize for responsive design.
- Implemented color schemes and margins optimized for both desktop and mobile viewing.
- Completed in 2022 and entirely self-directed.

## Web for document management Personal - 2023

- Created a user-friendly web page for browsing and managing various files.
- Utilized Flex and Grid to ensure a seamless experience across different devices.
- Programmed JavaScript functionality to allow for easy navigation across various sections, from log-in to admin mode.
- Demonstrated strong skills in both front-end design and backend programming.